oneclass.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | OneClass

Notesolution Inc. (o/a OneClass) (“OneClass”, “we”, “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy. The following policy describes how we collect, store, use and distribute information about our website, [www.oneclass.com](https://oneclass.com/) (the “Website”)and service users. 

Our goal is to collect, use and disclose information reasonably required to enable us to provide services to you, to maintain our customer/visitor lists and/or to respond to your inquiries or feedback and for other purposes further described in this Privacy Policy or in our Terms of Use. If you have provided us with contact information, we will maintain the confidentiality of your contact information and use it only for the purposes for which we have collected it, unless you agree that we may disclose it to other third parties (subject to the exclusions we have listed below). 

**By using the Website and/or the OneClass services, you consent to the collection and use by OneClass of personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not register to use any of our services or provide any personal information to us.**

### Important Terms: Minors

**Children Under the Age of 13.   ** This Website and the services are not meant for persons under 13 years of age and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information (as defined further below) from children who are 13 or younger. If we become aware that Personal Information has been collected from a person under the age of 13, we will take all necessary steps to remove any of that information from the Website and our databases immediately. 

**Children between 13 and 18 years of Age.   ** We ask that anyone who wishes to use the Website and services, who is between the ages of 13 and 18, gets permission from their parent(s) or guardian(s) before registering on OneClass and/or before sending us or anyone else any Personal Information about themselves. 

### Collection of Personal Information

OneClass may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, school or university information, credit card or other payment information, birth date and gender. Personal Information is collected in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for OneClass services, or if you desire to receive certain communications, updates, and information. At the time of collection we will set out clearly the information that we are collecting and the purposes for which we will use it. It is always your choice whether or not to provide personal information. If you choose not to provide requested personal information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Website and/or OneClass’s services and you may not be able to engage in certain activities or transactions through the Website. 

Certain content and features require a subscription or purchase through the Website. We currently use third party payment providers such as Stripe and Paypal and accordingly do not store your credit card information ourselves. For further information on the privacy practices of our third party payment processors please refer to their privacy policies when you set up payment. 

OneClass also may collect various information regarding the usage of the site by Users through means such as server logs and traffic information. This information may be aggregated and anonymized and in such form does not constitute personal information of Users. 

OneClass may also automatically receive general information that is contained in its server log files such as Users’ IP addresses and cookie information. When the visitor revisits OneClass, OneClass may recognize the visitor by their Internet cookie and customize the visitor’s experience according to their specific needs. Internet cookies may be declined by using the appropriate feature of the User’s Web client software, if available. 

OneClass may also record limited information for every search request and use that information to solve technical problems with its services and to calculate overall usage statistics. Not all information collected from Users constitutes personally information; however, such information may be associated with personally identifiable information provided to us by the Users. 

### Usage of Information

OneClass may use your personal information to contact and correspond with you regarding offerings of new products and services from OneClass (unless you have opted not to receive such updates); to enable, facilitate and enhance your use of the Website, and to meet legal and regulatory requirements. The information submitted to OneClass may also be used for conducting research in website productivity, marketing, advertising and effectiveness of OneClass. Users’ personal information will not be used for any purpose other than those mentioned herein without your consent. OneClass does not actively collect personally identifiable user information for the purpose of sale or marketing in a way that specifically identifies the individual. 

### Disclosure of Information

Identifiable or non-identifiable data may be disclosed or distributed to another party with which OneClass enters or reasonably may enter into a corporate transaction, such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition, or asset purchase, or to a third party pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other form of legal process, in response to a request by or on behalf of any provincial, federal government agency, department, or body. In the event of the sale of OneClass and its services, information obtained from Users may be transferred to a third party. OneClass is not responsible for, and will not be held liable for the conduct, actions, omissions, or information handling or dissemination practices during any corporate transactions. 

From time to time we may employ third parties to help us improve the Website and to provide various services (e.g. hosting, database management, maintenance, etc.). These third parties may have limited access to databases of user information or registered member information solely for the purpose of helping us to provide such services. 

### Security

OneClass uses commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that Users’ personal information is stored and maintained in a secure environment. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such Information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

### Law & Compliance

Our servers are located in Northern Virginia, accordingly your Personal Information may be available to the government or government agencies in the USA and your information may be accessed by the US government or agencies under a lawful order, irrespective of the safeguards we have put in place for the protection of your Personal Information. 

### Links to Other Sites

Through OneClass, you may be introduced to a variety of third party vendors and websites. The privacy policies of these third parties are not under our control and may differ from ours. The use of any information that you may provide to any third party, or the use of “cookie” technology by any third party, will be governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the website that you are visiting. If you have any doubts about the privacy of the information you are providing on another website, we recommend that you contact that website directly for more information and review its privacy policy. 

### Right to Change Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time and this will be reflected by the "last modified" date above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the OneClass service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.
